NATALIA SUAREZ

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



11-6051-1342

suarez.nataliam@gmail.com

Q Bs As, Argentina.

nataliasuarez.github.io

PROFILE

Software Developer with 5 years of experience in the IT world. I've dedicated my career to researching and programming in different technologies. My experience in different projects has allowed me to form agile teams with a leadership role.

SKILLS

- · Leadership Management
- Client communication
- Scrum Master
- Product Manager Tools
- Strong Communication
- Design Thinking, UX+
- Team builder
- Design Patterns
- Product delivery

EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEADER & FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

ExtraWorks. 2022 - 2023

- Tech stack: Flutter mobile, Flutter web, NEST.js, PostgreSQL.
 Others: push notifications, Stripe, socket.io, sendgrid.
- Scrum master: Sprint planning, Features roadmap, task definitions, effort estimation (Attlasian environment).
- App Store deploy: iOS and Android.
- UI definitions with Figma tools.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Blue Alba. 2020 - 2022

• Development with React.js, Java, PostgreSQL, Typescript. Others: state management, testing, hooks, storybooks.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER & COOP MEMBER

Cambá Coop. 2019 - 2020

 Work on multiple projects using Django, Node, Vue and React Native. Product discovery with customers and coop meetings.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Municipalidad de Alte Brown. 2018 - 2019

• PHP development with Symfony 4 and Posgresql.

EDUCATION

PRODUCT MANAGER

Coderhouse

2023

TEC. PROGRAMACIÓN (PRESENT)

UNQUI

2014